Guide to the Institute for Health Policy Studies - AIDS Resource Program Records
UCSF Library & CKM
- Subject Files, 1979-1989; Series 5; 5 cartons 1 box 12 folders
  - Workplace (Box:folder 14:12-13, 15:1-3)
    - Publications (Box:folder 15:1-3)
      - 1987 n.d. (Box:folder 15:1)
      - 1987-1988 n.d. (Box:folder 15:2)
      - 1987 n.d. (Box:folder 15:3)
  - World Health Organization, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 15:4)
  - SERIES 2: San Francisco General - Hospital Utilization Review (Challenges to MediCal denials), 1985-1986 (Box:folder 15:5)
    RESTRICTED
  - SERIES 5: Drug Therapies - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box:folder 15:6)